[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":183809,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":195944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":29025,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":224973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2775,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":227751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":[" 5"],"rt":7896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":235648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1237,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":236887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["5","6","0"],"rt":26740,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":263628,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1425,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":265056,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4780,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":269838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1021,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":270862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. I f the su m is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4241,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":275105,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":276116,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8841,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":284959,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1032,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":285993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3755,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":289750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":932,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":290684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> ( Remember , to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":11969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":302654,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1055,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":303712,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5 ","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4050,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":307763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":864,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":308628,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4905,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":313533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":898,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":314433,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":31665,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":346103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</ sub>). S imilarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":24750,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":370855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":125074,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":495932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":19827,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":515765,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><b r /> (Re member, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":12003,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":527769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1788,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":529558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7177,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":536735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1158,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":537894,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":8189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":546084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1079,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":547164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse  of 0 un der +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":7469,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":554634,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":17066,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":571701,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The numbers all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","response_history":["They all decrease in ","They all decrease in","They all decrease i","They all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The  all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The n all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The nu all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The num all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The numb all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The numbe all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The number all decrease by one in sequential order from 5.","The numbers all decrease by one in sequential order from 5."],"rt":120656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":692359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be perfor med star ting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":20448,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":712811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just  2.","rt":31251,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":744064,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":27472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":771537,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":12361,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":783900,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":102567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":886469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":34682,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":921153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":41239,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":962396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":11119,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":973520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":29664,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1003187,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>,  because  0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":8537,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1011726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"You can get other non-generators by combining the non-generators with themselves.","response_history":["You can get other non-generators by combining the non-generators with themselves."],"rt":246286,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1258015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":19837,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1277855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":16382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1294239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1011,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1295252,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":12586,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1307840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":12791,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1320632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":10876,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1331511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3754,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1335269,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1342997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine or larger than nine, I did not subtract nine. That left me with an answer of five.","response_history":["I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not b","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than 9, I did not subtract 9","I j ust adde d four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than 9, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of 5.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than , I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of 5.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than n, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of 5.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than ni, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of 5.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than nin, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of 5.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of 5.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of .","I just added four to one an d that w as five. Since it was not larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of f.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of fi.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of fiv.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not  larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not n larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not ni larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added fou r to one  and that was five. Since it was not nin larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine  larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine o larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine or larger than nine, I did not subtract nine, which left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine or larger than nine, I did not subtract nine. left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine or larger than nine, I did not subtract nine.  left  me with  an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine or larger than nine, I did not subtract nine. T left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine or larger than nine, I did not subtract nine. Th left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine or larger than nine, I did not subtract nine. Tha left me with an answer of five.","I just added four to one and that was five. Since it was not nine or larger than nine, I did not subtract nine. That left me with an answer of five."],"rt":74595,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1417596,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is larger than  nine, I  subtracted nine from it. That left me with an answer of three.","response_history":["I added eight to four and that was twelve. T","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is bigger than nine","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is l than nine","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is la than nine","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is lar than nine","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is larg than nine","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is large than nine","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is larger than nine","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is larger  than nine","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is larger than nine, I subtracted nine from it. That left w","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is larger than nine, I subtracted nine from it. That left me with an ans wer oi","I added eight to four and that was twelve. Since twelve is larger than nine, I subtracted nine from it. That left me with an answer of three."],"rt":54527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1472127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"The identity would be zero. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same result.","response_history":["The identity would be zero. This is because combining zero with anything will retiur","The identity would be zero. This is because combining zero with anything will retiu","The identity would be zero. This is because combining zero with anything will reti","The identity would be zero. This is because combining zero with anything will ret","The identity would be zero. This is because combining zero with  anythin g will return the same","The identity would be n. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same","The identity would be ni. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same","The identity would be nin. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same","The identity would be nine. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same result.","The identity would be z. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same result.","The identity would be ze. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same result.","The identity would be zer. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same result.","The identity would be zero. This is because combining zero with anything will return the same result."],"rt":152972,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1625131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5  under + <sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":50745,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1675941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":13456,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1689400,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, which is zero. That means that six is the inverse .","response_history":["To fidn the inverse, I would ","To finthe inverse, I would ","To findthe inverse, I would ","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Subtracting nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. S nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Si nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Sin nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I  would fi nd out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Sinc nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since  nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since i nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it nin e from t hat is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it  nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it i nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is  nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus t hree was . That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is n nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is ni nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nin nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it  is nine , nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine,  nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, y nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, yo nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To fin d the in verse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you  nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you h nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you ha nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you hav nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That  resulte d in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have  nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have t nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get  three pl us six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to  nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to  nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to s nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since i t is nin e, you have to su nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to sub nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subj nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to sub nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to su bt nine  from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtr nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtra nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtrac nine from that is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine fro m that i s zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that,  is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, w is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine fr om that,  wh is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, whi is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, whic is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, which is zero, which means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to  subtrac t nine from that, which is zero. means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, which is zero.  means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, which is zero. T means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, which is zero. Th means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you ha ve to su btract nine from that, which is zero. Tha means that six is the inverse.","To find the inverse, I would find out what nine minus three was. That resulted in six. Plugging it back in, you get three plus six which is nine. Since it is nine, you have to subtract nine from that, which is zero. That means that six is the inverse."],"rt":117871,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1807279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, if you keep combining two, you get all of the other numbers.","response_history":["Yes, if you combine 2","Yes, if you combine ","Yes, if you combine","Yes, if you combin","Yes, if you combi","Yes, if you comb","Yes, if you com","Yes, if you co","Yes, if you c","Yes, if you keep combining two, you get all of the other numbers."],"rt":248196,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":2055478,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, three is not a generator because you can not get all of the other numbers by combining it with itself.","response_history":["No, 3 ","No, 3","No, three is not a generator of ","No, three is not a generator of","No, three is not a generator o","No, three is not a generator ","No, three is not a generator because you can not get all of the other numbers by combining it with itself."],"rt":128723,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":2184203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, fiv e is not a generator because you can not get all of the numbers by combing it with itself.","response_history":["No, five is not a generator under ","No, five is not a generator under","No, five is not a generator unde","No, five is not a generator und","No, five is not a generator un","No, five is not a generator u","No, five is not a generator because you can not get all of the numbers by combing it we","No, five is not a generator because you can not get all of the numbers by combing it with itself."],"rt":70163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2254369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, six is not a generator because it cannot be combined with itself under this rule to get the rest of the numbers.","response_history":["No, six is not a generator und er nine  ","No, six is not a generator under nine","No, six is not a generator under nin","No, six is not a generator under ni","No, six is not a generator under n","No, six is not a generator under ","No, six is not a generator under","No, six is not a generator unde","No, six is not a generator und","No, six is not a generator un","No, six is not a generator u","No, six is not a generator because it cannot be con","No, six is not a generator because it cannot be combined with itsewlf under this rule to get the rest of the numbers.","No, six is not a generator because it cannot be combined with itself under this rule to get the rest of the numbers."],"rt":99112,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2353483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of.  If you  need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":17964,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2371449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+_n1=0","response_history":["1+\"+_n","1++_n","1+_n","1+n","1+_n=0","1+_n1=0"],"rt":172766,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2544217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Whatistheformulafortheinverseofanelementxunder+<sub>n</sub>?Pleaseexplaininwordshowyougotyouranswer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"Theformulawouldxplus+_nequalszerobecausetheinversehastobeaddedtothevalueattachedto\"+_n\"toequaltheidentity,whichiszero.","response_history":["Theforumlawould","Theformlawould","Theformulawouldxplus\"+_n","The formula would x plus +_n e","The formula would x plus +_n equals zero because the inverse has to be added to the value attached to \"+_n\" to equal the identity.","The formula would x plus +_n equals zero because the inverse has to be added to the value attached to \"+_n\" to equal the identity, which is zero."],"rt":90257,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2634476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Since +_n can be any positive counting number, any positive counting number could be a generator.","response_history":["It could be whatever the initial number is","Since \"+_n","Since+_ncanbeanyc","Since+_ncanbeanyposy","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumberm","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumberm","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,itcould","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,itcoul","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,itcou","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,itco","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,itc","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,it","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,it","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,i","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbethe","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbethe","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeth","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbet","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","I+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","I+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","It+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ith+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithi+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithin+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithink+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithink+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithinkt+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithinktha+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithinkthat+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithinkthat+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithinkthats+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithinkthatsi+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Ithinkthatsin+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","S+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Si+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Sin+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Sinc+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator.","Since+_ncanbeanypositivecountingnumber,anypositivecountingnumbercouldbeagenerator."],"rt":132189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2766666,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Trueorfalse:Ifxisanoddnumber,itmustbeageneratorunder+<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2773596,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Trueorfalse:Ifxisanevennumber,itmustnotbeageneratorunder+<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2781290,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Trueorfalse:Ifxisnotageneratorunder+<sub>n</sub>,xmustdividen.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2787771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Trueorfalse:Ifxisnotageneratorunder+<sub>n</sub>,xmustbeamultipleofadivisorofn.Pleaseexplaininwordswhyyouransweriscorret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"Ithinkthat'sfalsebecause+_ncanbeanypositivenumber,whichmeansthatanyofitsdivisorscouldbeamultipleofit.","response_history":["This","Thi","Th","T","Ithinkthat'sfalsebecause\"+_n","I think that's false because +_n can be anut","I think that's false because +_n can be anu","I think that's false because +_n can be any posiutve number, which means that any of its divisors could be a multiple of it.","I think  that's f alse because +_n can be any positve number, which means that any of its divisors could be a multiple of it.","I think that's false because +_n can be any positive number, which means that any of its divisors could be a multiple of it."],"rt":79391,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2867163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":7310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2874475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I think this is always correct since +_n can be any positive number and can change to make any number into a generator.","response_history":["I think this is alwasy correct since","I think this is alwas correct since","I think this is alwa correct since","I think this is alway correct since","I think this is always correct since \"+_n","Ithinkthisisalwayscorrectsince+_ncanbeanypositivenumberandcanchangetomakeanynumberintoa","Ithinkthisisalwayscorrectsince+_ncanbeanypositivenumberandcanchangetomakeanynumberintoagenerator."],"rt":62583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2937059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Ifanelementxisnotageneratorunder+<sub>n</sub>,isx+<sub>n</sub>xageneratorunder+<sub>n</sub>always,sometimes,ornever?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":12453,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2949513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"Wewouldliketoaskyousomequestionsaboutyourbackground.Pleasepress\"Continue\"tocontinue.","rt":1574,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2951088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Whatisyourage?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"27","response_history":["27"],"rt":3104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2954193,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Whatisyourlevelofeducation?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Didnotgraduatehighschool","Highschooldiploma","Somecollege,nodegree","AssociatesDegree","BachelorsDegree","Somegraduateschool,nodegree","MastersDegree","Doctorate,M.D.,etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"BachelorsDegree","response_history":["BachelorsDegree"],"rt":2508,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2956702,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Whatisthemostadvancedmathclassyou'vecompleted?Ifyouhavemultipleclassesandyou'renotsurewhichoneismostadvanced,pleaselistthem.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"AlgebraII","response_history":["AlgebraII"],"rt":15029,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2971733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Howfamiliarareyouwiththeconceptofmodulararithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1-neverheardofit","2-heardofitbutdidn'tknowwhatitwas","3-seenitusedorexplained","4-useditbutnotoftenorrecently","5-usedit,rememberandunderstandit"],"correct_response":"1", "response":"3-seenitusedorexplained","response_history":["3-seenitusedorexplained"],"rt":4318,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2976052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Howfamiliarareyouwiththeconceptofamathematicalgroup?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1-neverheardofit","2-heardofitbutdidn'tknowwhatitwas","3-seenitusedorexplained","4-useditbutnotoftenorrecently","5-usedit,rememberandunderstandit"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4-useditbutnotoftenorrecently","response_history":["3-seenitusedorexplained","4-useditbutnotoftenorrecently"],"rt":12780,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2988833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"DoyoufeelyoulearnedsomethingfromthisHIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1-notatall","2-somewhat","3-definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2-somewhat","response_history":["2-somewhat"],"rt":4970,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2993805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"DoyoufeelyouunderstoodtheconceptsinthisHIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1-notatall","2-somewhat","3-definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1-notatall","response_history":["1-notatall"],"rt":8750,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3002558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"DidyouenjoythisHIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1-notatall","2-somewhat","3-definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1-notatall","response_history":["1-notatall"],"rt":2787,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3005348,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Whatisyourgender?","response_type":"multi" ,"response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Other","response_history":["Other"],"rt":2069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3007419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Whatis/areyournativelanguage(s)?(Thelanguagesspokeninyourhouseholdwhenyouwereachild.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"AmericanEnglish","response_history":["AmericanEnglish"],"rt":8455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3015877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"DidyouusepenandpaperatanypointonthisHIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No,IdidnotuseapenorpaperduringthisHIT.","response_history":["No,IdidnotuseapenorpaperduringthisHIT."],"rt":12576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3028455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"DoyouhaveanycommentsonthisHIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmath,andespeciallythesekindsofconcepts,isnotmystrength.","response_history":["Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtry","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymy","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymy","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrym","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmathandco","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmathandc","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmathandespeciallythesekindsofconceptsarenotmyforte.","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmathandespeciallythesekindsofconceptsarenotmystreangth.","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmathandespeciallythesekindsofconceptsarenotmystrength.","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmath,andespeciallythesekindsofconceptsarenotmystrength.","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmath,andespeciallythesekindsofconcepts,arenotmystrength.","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmath,andespeciallythesekindsofconcepts,inotmystrength.","Thiswasaninterestingsurvey,butitwasverydifficult,especiallytowardtheend.Ididtrymybest,butmath,andespeciallythesekindsofconcepts,isnotmystrength."],"rt":55361,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3083817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]